hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Krakowski for those of you that
I haven't met yet I help course creators
and coaches scale their businesses to
seven and eight figures and I help
beginning coaches and course creators
make their first six figures in their
business this podcast is all about the
mindset and strategies that you need to
be able to succeed as a coach or course
creator I also do live events that I
highly recommend that you check out five
day events as well as single day events
where I go over specific topics that
serve coaches and course creators to
help them grow if you haven't checked
out my YouTube channel yet there's close
to a thousand videos on there on every
single topic Master Class level every
video is like its own mini class to help
coaches and course creators get more
sales as well as this podcast has over
185 episodes designed to help coaches
and course creators succeed and make
money and so tons tons of great
resources for you out there if you're
listening to this for the first time
that I have if you're a course creator
or coach you can learn to make money for
free with the resources that I put out
there and if you want to join my group
coaching program right now there's
usually the doors are closed there's a
waiting list you can jump on the waiting
list for that it's less than five
thousand dollars a year to jump in and
so keep that in mind if you're somebody
that says hey maybe I'll be willing to
make an investment with Jeremiah to jump
in and get some coaching that I need to
get the clients that I want the client
growth accelerator is going to help you
do that it's over my website
jeremicorkowski.com now today I want to
talk about talking to the right people
talking to the right prospects and who
to actually talk to here's the thing I
made a post on my social media today and
this is kind of dovetailing on a topic
that I've been thinking about
listen if if you're not going to spend
money with me I don't care about what
you want
I only do stuff for people that give me
money
now you might be listening to the same
well Jeremiah I haven't paid you any
money yet that's great however
because I have now hundreds of clients
I've worked with I look at patterns of
what do my paid clients need for me what
are their desires what do they want to
learn and how can I help them and so I'm
only ever speaking to people who have
either already paid me money or at least
fit into the pattern and qualifications
of those that have paid me money meaning
there's a group of people out there
who want to learn how to grow their
coaching business by going to
conferences and doing coffee meetups
I can't help those people and I won't
even talk about those topics
there's other coaches that will teach
you how to do that
that's not in in the framework of what I
help people do so I don't even go into
that topic or serve it and if somebody
asks me about it I will usually direct
them to somebody else who's written a
book on that topic
because I'm not even gonna spend a
minute of my time talking about
something that those who actually buy
from me
don't want to learn
so I only ever talk about stuff that
buyers care about and I ignore the
desires of everybody else I neglect them
I ignore them they they mean nothing to
me they're meaningless to me they're now
they're great people they're they have
value they're human beings like I'm not
saying that like they're valueless
people but like to me in my business
I'm only focused on
people who have paid me money and what
they want
or people that fit the same pattern as
those who have paid me money
maybe they haven't paid me money yet but
what do those people want it's a it's a
psychological profile that I've created
over the years based off of what people
have told me that they want to learn
based off of who is actually in my
coaching program based off of who is
actually listening to my podcast based
off of who is actually giving me money
to buy my courses and coaching from me
and so everything that I'll talk about
in my business
is only ever related to what those
people care about
I don't talk about anything else and so
that's the thing for you as a coach as a
mentor as a trainer
every single thing that you talk about
should only be based on what your buyers
care about
not just the prospects not just the look
you lose not just the questioners not
just the critics here's the thing you're
gonna have a lot of critics in your life
especially if you go out there to build
a coaching business people that say that
you should be doing things a certain way
people that are going to criticize you
and say that you're wrong people are
going to say that your methodologies are
wrong if you spend your energy serving
those people communicating to those
people and they're never going to spend
any money with you you're going to go
broke and here's the thing I ended up
doing that so in the beginning in my
business a lot of my content is geared
towards a very wide range of people
and I've honed in more and more my Niche
more and more which by the way side note
if you're like I don't know how to find
my Niche you're not really going to ever
have it figured out perfectly even after
years and years and years because you're
going to be constantly refining your
Niche more and more based off of who's
paying you money the more you Niche down
the more you can charge
I haven't even niched down enough to
charge what I want to in my business yet
and you can make six figures with a very
generic niche
you can make eight figures by really
honing in deeply and specifically as to
who you can help versus trying to serve
everybody out there so for instance
if somebody wants to come to me and they
want to argue and they I just I have I
have I have
um earplugs on to critical people
I have earplugs on to anybody who wants
to criticize what I'm doing I have
earplugs on to people that are extremely
analytical
that are extremely
um
this is the right way to do it and if I
can't do it the right way then I won't
do anything at all because the truth is
I'm never going to convince those people
to do anything different
and the people who I actually help
are recovering perfectionists so I work
with a lot of recovering perfectionists
because I used to be that way
where I was afraid to put my business
out there unless everything was perfect
I was afraid to launch anything unless
it was all perfect
and so
when I stopped worrying about doing all
the right things perfectly I actually
started doing more of the right things
in my business and one of those things
is just ignoring the the the people that
are not going to be buyers from you just
ignoring the people that are not
actually coming to you to ask questions
in the beginning when you're not
spending money you want to focus on okay
who are the people that are actually
coming to me for free to listen to me
who are actually asking questions that's
gonna be a wider range of people start
there but then pay attention to very
quickly the ones who are actually giving
you money the ones that are actually
spending money with you
what do they have in common that the
ones that haven't spent money with you
don't and then ignore the desires that
only the ones that haven't spent money
with you have and focus on the desires
of just the ones that are spending money
with you
when you do that you make a whole lot
more money you attract a whole lot more
people because you're specifically
talking to a very specific type of
person who will spend money with you and
you will end up attracting them more
often with your virtual events with your
courses with your coaching with your
content with your training and you're
going to produce results because you're
going to be talking to the right people
I go another level up from this okay so
you have buyers right
but then you also have results
generators
and so in my life who are the people
that have actually generated results
and how can I talk to the gap between
where people are and where they need to
be to get results to help Elevate them
to help raise them up at that level I
truly believe anybody who's listening to
my podcast can make over a million
dollars a month in coaching courses I do
that's a big statement
because I attract the type of people
that have what it takes that are willing
to take action
that have a vision they have a plan that
that can see that far into the future
now here's the thing though if you're
not going to take action in your
business you're not going to do anything
you're not going to make any money and
so that's reality check here right
let's be realistic you actually have to
do something you actually have to put
yourself out there you actually have to
show up
if you're not going to show up you can't
expect the results of somebody who shows
up
you can't get paid for work you didn't
do
that's a big important factor now here's
the thing you might have done a lot of
great things in the past I'm talking to
people that maybe resonate with me I
have a lot of experience right I've
built multiple eight-figure businesses
am I getting payday figures right now no
because I haven't personally done the
same work in my business as the clients
that I've helped and so now I'm getting
to that level in my own business I don't
expect to get paid for work that I
didn't do
and a lot of the work that that you got
to do is you got to be able to create
videos create video content where you're
connecting with and communicating to
your target Prospect your Target
customer the people that are most likely
to become purchasers with you and ignore
everybody else in your messaging
ignore everybody else
blinders onto what they want
when you do this
you will upset people
you will offend some people
uh just naturally because they're gonna
be like that's not true that's not right
that won't work in my business well
okay great awesome you're right here's
the thing just agree with them and let
them move on like you don't need to
prove yourself to them it's not it's not
worth your energy trying to prove to
people that are committed to
misunderstanding you and trying to
debate you it's not your job to make
sure that they agree with you
okay
I had like three people today do that
um like literally on social media you're
wrong that doesn't work that way
okay
I'm gonna go work with coaches that want
to make six figures I don't need to talk
to you
because
well I'm sure you're a great person
well I'm sure you were a nice kind
individual uh you're not you're not a
buyer in my business you're not
qualified yet you're you have you you've
disqualified Yourself by saying that
that way
oh
and so
by doing that
you will hone in more and more and more
on who is actually going to purchase
from you in your business and you'll
have to work a whole lot less it takes a
whole lot less energy
which is great which is good you
actually want to work less your goal as
a coach as a course creator is to work
less
a lot of people think that the goal is
to work more now the goal is to make
enough money so that you can literally
hire out every single role in your
business
and it runs itself without you and you
and you systematize everything and you
build out a system and that's what takes
businesses to seven figures you can get
to six figures as a solopreneur easy all
day long
not a big deal not very hard
seven figures takes a team
100 percent
100 it's very hard to solo to solo it up
to seven figures
then that's just a reality that's just
that's just how life is that's just how
things are there's some people that can
do it
well why would you why would you want to
like if you can literally
you know pay
uh sixty dollars a week to somebody in
the Philippines to edit your videos for
you from onlinejobs.ph why wouldn't you
why would you spend 20 hours editing it
yourself
three dollars an hour that's what I pay
my video editor in the Philippines
that's the rate that they've asked me to
pay them too I didn't even negotiate
that down that's like that's like a
that's like a good wage even over there
which is awesome I use this website
called
onlinejobs.ph for the Philippines
uh to do that and and they're a great
resource to to find people uh better
than upwork better than a lot of these
other resources that are out there it's
a great job board with very talented
people virtual assistants
um
Graphics designers I'm about to hire I
think two two more people off of here
soon
I have somebody that actually does my
Jasper stuff for me and does my Facebook
ads and then edits all my videos
I'm still writing copy I'm still
recording content
but I I have a team that's helping me
actually
execute that's helping me actually
create stuff that's helping me
um to do all that in the beginning you
don't need that you can use canva for
your graphics
use the templates type in your text
use your cell phone to edit videos you
don't even you don't really even need to
edit much video in the beginning at all
you can make six figures without editing
videos
you don't need to edit a whole lot
Jasper AI is a very important tool I
think that everybody needs to have
because the amount of time it will take
you to write that level of sales copy on
your own it's just it's just there's no
it's just stupid to try to figure it out
on your on your own
you might as well use resources like
Jasper AI
um to do that
to get results okay
and so again
that's me I'm talking to specifically
buyers in my business people that have
actually bought from me and I'm thinking
about specifically
um a couple of my clients right now that
I know are gonna listen to this episode
um
I'm gonna say this
don't allow
religious beliefs
to prevent you from using tools that
exist
um
yes it's great to use your intuition yes
it's great to use the Holy Spirit to
write your sales copy
but if you're refusing to use Jasper
because of that reason that might be a
religious route that's not helping you
um or don't let your pride do that
if you're like I'm an expert on this
topic and so I'm not gonna let some AI
write for me don't let your pride do
that let the AI write your marketing
copy it's better than you it's better
than me it's worth it okay
and so really that's what it boils down
to it boils down to Pride and ego and
again needing to do things the right way
well I'm better that like we gotta get
rid of those those beliefs in our brain
of trying to fight for position
fight for you know why I've worked this
hard in my journey and so I'm not going
to let some artificial intelligence do
my job for me
that's that stinking thinking is going
to keep you if you're that's gonna keep
you broke it really will it's going to
keep you from actually making the kind
of money that you want to make I don't
even write my
social media captions anymore
I have my assistant take my videos
transcribe them and then filter them
through Jasper to write my captions for
all of my tick tocks and stuff because
I don't need to they have a tick tock
generator that's great that does great
captions I love them
and so
for you in your business
do what you need to do to get sales
to get customers
if you're not getting sales and
customers all the other stuff doesn't
matter
and focus on
who are the people that you know are
going to give you money with all of your
messaging with all of your marketing
with all of your offers with all of your
efforts with all of your content
when you do that
growth will start to happen
all right listen if this has helped you
share it with somebody subscribe to the
podcast
and make sure to jump on one of the free
live events that we're doing coming up
consider joining the client growth
accelerator if you're not in there it's
a group coaching program for coaches
trainers mentors and course creators
that want to make six and seven figures
in their business
and I can help you do that as well in
there
I want to create over a thousand
millionaire coaches
that starts with me creating over a
thousand six figure coaches
you know what you guys have just seen it
here live I'm gonna probably change that
goal
yes I want to make a thousand
millionaire for coaches but first off I
gotta make a thousand six figure earners
and so my goal is I want to help a
thousand people make six figures I might
even come up with like a a six-figure
or a seven figure award kind of like I
like like how click funnels does that
an award for people when they reach that
certain level that I can award them for
their funnel from taking our training
and doing that
I think that would be really cool
some of the people can work towards
something that's tangible something that
certifies them
so I'm just processing ideas
let me know if that's something that
interests you
let me know in the in the comments or DM
me or send me a message or whatever all
right I'll see you on one of our events
I'll see you on one of our coaching
calls grow your life everybody we'll
talk soon
[Music]
[Applause]